export const quizData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about callbacks?",
    options: [
      "A callback is a function that passes to another function as an argument.",
      "A callback is not a function that passes to another function as an argument",
      "None of above",
    ],
    answer: [
      "A callback is a function that passes to another function as an argument.",
    ],
  },

  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?",
    options: ["toString()", "toFixed()", "toLocaleString()", "toPrecision()"],
    answer: "toString()",
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question: "what thread is JavaScript",
    options: ["single thread", "multithread", "none of above"],
    answer: "single thread",
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "If we declare a variable, let test = 1, then later, reassign, stating test = 2, what will happen?",
    options: [
      "test will equal 2",
      "test will equal 1",
      "JavaScript will raise a TypeError",
      "test will equal undefined",
    ],
    answer: "test will equal 2",
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What does undefined value mean in javascript?",
    options: [
      "undefine means a variable has been declared but has not yet been assigned a value",
      "Undefine means function didnâ€™t return any value",
      "All above",
      "None of above",
    ],
    answer: "All of above",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "In your JavaScript code, how do you find out which character occurs at the 5th position in a string, How are you?",
    options: ["Substring()", " String()", "Stringlength()", " CharAt()"],
    answer: "ChatAt()",
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "How do you prompt users with messages and at the same time requesting user inputs?",
    options: ["Alert()", "Display()", " Prompt()", "Confirm()"],
    answer: "Prompt()",
  },
  {   
    id:7,
    question:"How to debug JavaScript",
    options:[
      "Use breakpoints on Chrome DevTool","console.log()", 
      "debugger", "All of above",
      "None of Above" ],
    answer:"All of above"
},
{   id:8,
    question:"What is difference between agrument and parameter?",
    options:[
        "Agrument is a variable declare in a function, but parameter is a actual value that pass to function", 
        "Parameter is a variable declare in a function, but agrument is a actual value that pass to function", 
        "All of above",
        "None of above"],
    answer: "Parameter is a variable declare in a function, but agrument is a actual value that pass to function"
},
{   
    id:9,
    question:"setTimeOut() is executed by Web API",
    options:["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
},
{   
    id:10,
    question:"Is Javascript not asynchronous",
    options:["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
},
{   id:11,
    question:"What is new in ES6?",
    options:["Symbol data type", "Let and const keyword", "Arrow function", "B and C, but not A", "All of above", "None of Above"],
    answer: "All of Above"
},
{   
   id:12,
   question:"What is lexical scope?",
   options:["A variable can be access by all other functions ", "A variable can be only determined by the region where it creates and define", "All of above", "None of above"],
   answer: "A variable can be only determined by the region where it creates and define"
},
{   
   id:13,
   question:"What is lexical scope?",
   options:["A variable can be access by all other functions ", "A variable can be only determined by the region where it creates and define", "All of above", "None of above"],
   answer: "A variable can be only determined by the region where it creates and define"
}
];

